The cargo's coming into
the city from the east.
We're taking the whole vehicle.
Haul's two 'n' a half mil.
Pot o' gold with the usual split.
This one's definitely
the biggest job I've ever taken.
Target's a corp, ain't it?
Three guesses which one it is.
Arasaka, of course.
Half a mil a head's nice 'n' all,
but I ain't even sure if it's worth it.
Really think five of us is enough?
Security footprint
on the convoy's peculiarly small.
Arasaka's posted a limited crew to cast
a short shadow, keep a low profile.
We'll strike the metal where it's soft.
I dunno, man…
Let's not overthink this.
Smash, grab, deliver. It's what we do.
Business as usual.
Business as usual my ass.
You think he'll withstand
the cyberskeleton?
Arasaka does. After seeing his chemistry
mesh so well with the Sandevistan.
Tanaka wanted him back in the Academy
so he could test the cyberskeleton on him.
And this girl was trying to
bury that information
so no one would come after him.
That's how I see it.
Frying Tanaka tied up a loose end.
Maine and Dorio were just
collateral damage in her schemes.
That's one way of putting it…
So much carnage for one so petite.
How many did she kill just to save one?
Dove a little deeper and found that
she used to work for Arasaka.
They groomed her
to mine data in the Old Net.
Guess that's how she's been able to
get past Arasaka's ICE.
This is perfect.
What a wonderful surprise.
We can dangle her in front of Arasaka.
Our fast-lane ticket up
the corporate rungs!
Didn't see you as
such a simp corpo-climber.
Is that really so strange?
What are fixers
if not glorified pet owners
who keep their mercenary hounds well fed?
The only way to succeed in Night City
is to get in with the corporations.
I'll require your continued assistance.
Gonna make me keep digging
this hole deeper?
This is a great opportunity
for you as well.
I have corporate amnesty for
the Tanaka incident… But what about you?
You're as slimy as ever.
Let's play nice for old time's sake.
How often do we get to work with Arasaka
and stick it to Militech with one hand?
Arasaka wouldn't object.
I'll negotiate for your immunity
and commission.
Never trust a soul in Night City.
Trusting fools deserve
the hand they're dealt…
Is David a bargaining chip as well?
Naturally. I've conjured a plan.
I'll pitch them both to Arasaka.
What's up with the emergency meeting?
Faraday's come through.
It's our biggest gig yet.
Huge risk, huge return. Turn back now
if you're not ready to face the heat.
I'm counting on you too, Kiwi.
Sure.
Yo, granny and gramps
can bench this round.
Think your little chicken legs'll
reach the pedals?
Kiss my ass.
Give us the brief.
'Saka put on a small,
heavy-duty security squad.
But they'll split. Half'll go after
a diversion squad commissioned by Faraday.
Diversion squad?
A decoy, basically. Though that's probably
not in the brief Faraday gave them.
Oh.
Typical Faraday handiwork.
Of course, there's no way to tell
if we're also a decoy…
Bitch!
Good, good. We've got 'em
nice and split. What's the call?
Main target's off the road.
We've got the high ground.
Put her in gear, Falco!
Alright!
Let's hit it!
Hey, David. Car's all warmed and ready…
David!
Are these all immunosuppressants?
Can you fetch my mom's jacket for me?
We're calling off the gig!
Rebecca… I got a favor to ask…
You better knock it--
Becca, I can't ask anyone else…
Rebecca?
Puppy-dog eyes! Knew I'm
a sucker for the vulnerable, didn't ya?!
Don't use your fucking Sandevistan.
You hear me?
Okay, okay…
One down!
Alright, we're right on the target's ass!
I'll hack into the brake.
Hold on, we got a tail!
Can't even get a peek out there!
Leave it to me!
Hey! Don't use your Sandevistan…
Fucking deaf, that one?!
You're a real piece of work!
Damn you, David!
Everyone good?
Hey 'stache! Do we look good?!
Look.
It's still going?!
ICE is as thick as the armor.
Can't hack it.
Then I'll hit 'em from the front.
Seriously, knock it--
Fucking tired of being ignored!
…on autopilot!
So please.
Sit back, relax, and enjoy the show.
Not good.
-We'd better stop it fast before it falls.
-What?!
Alright… What are ya gonna do, David?
We're right on the edge…
Falco! Pull up closer!
Easier said than done…
What do we do?!
I'll shoot it if you won't!
That's right. Easy does it, David.
No one here to slap sense into you now.
Make a choice.
You're special, remember?
Brake!
Slam on 'em!
No way.
Th-That's how it's done.
Bit my tongue…
How nice.
They send an executive-class AV
to collect a street girl?
You really must be
their precious, lost toy.
Still no response from Lucy?
Ugh. What's one more runner
gonna do for us at this point?
You gonna pay her from your pot?
How's it going over there?
Few more minutes to break the lock.
Is it just me or does it bother you
that this carrier was unmanned?
You sure it's an Arasaka vehicle?
If you're so worried,
just take the cargo and go.
We're all waiting on you.
Quit the yapping and let's go get our car.
Sheesh. Didn't strike me back when
we were going after the carrier,
but we'd be fishes in a barrel
if anyone tried to shoot us out here.
Jesus, old man. Nervous fart like you
doesn't deserve that cowboy 'stache!
You'd go weak in the knees if I shaved.
Ew! Gonna kick it off!
Stop dodging, old man!
Looks like the decoy failed.
We've got company!
What?!
That a Basilisk?
And a missile carrier!
You're shitting me…
Militech!
What the fuck?!
Why're we being steamrolled by Militech?!
Faraday's a Militech-man, ain't he?
The fishiness is really starting to reek!
It's open!
That was quick!
Take cover inside. Hurry!
What in the seven hells is this…?
This is what Faraday paid Maine to find?
So what is it?
A cyberskeleton. Military implant.
Military…
You mean like David's Sandevistan?
From what I hear,
it's a whole different caliber.
Hey. This kid's Sandy ain't
nothing to turn your nose up at either.
First time I'm hearing about this.
Believe me or don't.
Arasaka thinks they can overtake Militech
if this thing hits the market.
But they've kept its development
on the down-low.
Most of its information
was concentrated under Tanaka's wing.
I don't know how,
but Faraday got wind of this,
and promised to leak this tech to
Militech to get himself a nice deal.
Not every day you get to fly
above Night City at your leisure.
It must be a nice change of scenery
from your usual ice-filled baths.
What do you say?
Want to help me make your boy fly?
What?
Incoming call from Lucy.
Now is seriously not the time!
No time. Militech's coming.
How do you know that? Where are you?
They're after me too.
Lucy!
What did she say?
"Use the cyberskeleton
if you want to survive."
The fuck?
She didn't seem herself though.
Sure about that?
Someone's after her too.
I've gotta install it.
Whole truck's a mobile installation unit.
That deck's got the installer all set up.
You are not gonna install this thing!
I gotta get us out of this!
Are you insane?! You don't even know
what this hunk of metal can do!
I don't see any other option.
Besides me knocking you the fuck out?!
I'm gonna go get our car.
I'll go with.
Thanks!
Last time I installed something that
wasn't mine, Maine beat the shit outta me.
Some things just don't change!
Don't! Wait…
You fucking gonk!
Why don't you ever listen?!
What's Militech waiting for?
Kiwi, you able to get eyes on…
Sorry.
What?!
Did you truly think
we would put no failsafe in place?
Shall I open a second neural port
in the back of your skull?
-I'm afraid she's currently indisposed.
-Faraday?!
I trust the job is going well?
Fuck you, put Lucy back on!
This chairjock bitch should feel grateful
to be kissing the ground.
I was worried I might've
overscrambled her brain.
Take your fucking foot off her!
Don't be so serious.
I'm just having a ball of a time.
Besides, I won't have to lift a finger
when Arasaka's done with her.
Faraday!
You're rapidly degenerating!
At this rate, you're gonna
go psycho in seconds!
Elite Militech forces are closing in.
Install the soft, use the cyberskeleton,
David. Lead your crew to safety.
Personally, I think it's beyond you.
Clearly Arasaka sees something I don't.
If you're truly so special, boy,
show me what you can do. Survive.
I'll kill him! I'm gonna go kill him!
I'll kill him! I'll kill him…
I'm gonna fucking--
You okay?
I'm gonna go save Lucy.
Uhh… Nope, I think your brain's fried.
Faraday's double-crossed us.
He's got Lucy.
Huh? What do you mean?
That fucker.
I'm gonna fucking put him in the ground!
I swear, he's gonna fucking die…
David…
Falco! What happened?
Kiwi got me.
What?!
She led us into a trap.
Oh, that hag. She's in it too?
She's a fucking flatline
when I see her next!
Here we go again!
Shit!
Militech's really out to kill us!
I've never seen anything like this.
How can anyone walk with this on?
Two compact thrusters're built in.
Same kind you get on an AV.
On top of that, Arasaka engineered in
a gravity modification prototype.
It can generate unidirectional
grav fields, magnetic forces, too…
That's the magnetic force generator?
Hot damn!
He just mowed a small squad down!
He's using his Sandevistan, too.
He's flying!
That's the gravitational field?
But this tech hasn't left
its testing stage.
The controls are too complex.
There's no guarantee that the equipper's
nerves will be able to withstand it.
It requires an insane level
of mental fortitude against implants.
A one-way ticket to
cyberpsychosis, you mean.
They got him?!
David…
He's still going!
His body is, but…
The more he uses it, the closer he will be
to overloading his cyberware capacity.
But in exchange, the short-term
power it generates is…
unlike anything devised
on this side of sanity.
David?
We're going after Faraday
for betraying us.
And we're gonna save Lucy.
You say that but…
Equal share of the pot.
That's my style.
Alright, buddy.
Onwards to hell.